Hello, my name is Anil Chaudhary. I am 55
years old. Due to my loss due to Covid,
I have been running a small business of exporting homemade spices with my wife for the past few years.
Without marine transit insurance, it becomes
very difficult to bear the losses in this business.
Orders come in from abroad at any time and we
even prepare our goods, but
due to insurance and its delayed documentation, shipments are often
delayed and customers get angry.
I learned from the traders in the market that with
ICC Lombard Marine Transit Insurance,
now there is no documentation, no
fuss. You can get a policy in just a few minutes,
that too with just a few clicks.
ICC.lombard.com is your
true digital partner. ICC Lombard
Business Insurance Solutions like Marine
Transit, Roof, Health & Fire etc. promise to
protect the businesses of the country's MSMEs
and we salute their courage.